Elvis	PER
Presley	PER
was	O
born	O
on	O
January	O
8	O
,	O
1935	O
,	O
in	O
Tupelo	LOC
,	O
Mississippi	LOC
,	O
the	O
son	O
of	O
Gladys	PER
Love	PER
and	O
Vernon	PER
Elvis	PER
Presley	PER
,	O
in	O
the	O
two-room	O
shotgun	O
house	O
built	O
by	O
Vernon	PER
's	O
father	O
in	O
preparation	O
for	O
the	O
child	O
's	O
birth	O
.	O

